tennischannel.com 2016-05-06

# Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy
LAST UPDATED AND EFFECTIVE DATE: MAY 1, 2014
PLEASE READ THIS PRIVACY POLICY (THIS “PRIVACY POLICY”) THOROUGHLY BEFORE USING OUR WEBSITE, APPLICATIONS OR
ANY OTHER THE TENNIS CHANNEL, INC. (“TENNIS CHANNEL,” “WE,” OR “US”) SERVICE FOR AN EXPLANATION OF HOW WE WILL
TREAT YOUR PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION, AS YOU ARE CONSENTING TO THE INFORMATION COLLECTION AND
USE PRACTICES AS OUTLINED IN THIS PRIVACY POLICY AND TO THE COLLECTION, PROCESSING AND MAINTENANCE OF THIS
INFORMATION BY YOUR VISITING AND USING THE SERVICES AND/OR BY PARTICIPATING IN THE EMAIL PROGRAMS DESCRIBED
HEREIN.
Your privacy is very important to Tennis Channel, a company incorporated under Delaware law, with its registered address at 2850 Ocean Park Blvd., Suite 150, Santa
Monica, CA 90405, and we are committed to securing your privacy. This Privacy Policy applies to all of the websites owned and/or operated by Tennis Channel, its owned
and/or operated affiliated businesses and other websites operated under the Tennis Channel brand which link to this Privacy Policy and any mobile-accessible internet or
WAP sites owned and/or operated by Tennis Channel (collectively, the “Site”), and any downloadable mobile application owned and/or operated by Tennis Channel
available from third party application storefronts (the “Application(s)”) (collectively, the “Services”). This Privacy Policy describes the treatment of information provided or
collected on the Services where this Privacy Policy is posted, how we collect information from you, how we use it, and with whom we share it. This Privacy Policy applies
(i) whether you are accessing the Services via a personal computer, tablet, mobile device or any other technology or devices now known or hereinafter developed (each a
“Device”) and (ii) only to information collected online and does not apply to information collected or obtained offline by any other means. If you do not agree with this
Privacy Policy, please do not participate in the Services or any features, activities or services offered through the Services. Your use of any part of the Services indicates
your acceptance of this Privacy Policy and of the collection and use of your personally identifiable information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy
will remain in full force and effect, even if your use of or participation in the Site or any particular Service, feature, function or promotional activity offered through the
Services terminates, expires, ceases, is suspended or deactivated for any reason. This Privacy Policy is a part of and is incorporated into the Tennis Channel.com Terms
of Use.
1. Types of Information We Collect
2. How We Collect Your Information
3. How We Use and Share Your Information
4. Your Controls and Choices
5. Children's Privacy
6. Security
7. Changes to This Privacy Policy
8. Comments and Questions
9. California Privacy Rights
1. Types of Information We Collect
When you access the Services, we collect personally identifiable information that specifically identifies you or can be used to contact you. The personal information we
collect may include, but is not limited to, full name, address, zip code, telephone number(s), email address, date of birth, cable provider, gender, username and password,
location data, other personal data as detailed in this Privacy Policy and data that may be requested from and provided by you, and, in certain instances, your payment
card information. In addition, we may also collect other anonymous information about you that may not allow someone to personally identify you. When using the Services,
you may be asked to provide various types of personally identifiable information or anonymous information to enhance your experience on the Services. We may use
personal and anonymous information to create a third type of information, aggregate information.
To sign up for or participate in any features or functions, you may be required to provide us with certain personally identifiable information or other information about you in
order for us to personalize and/or allow you to use such features and functions. For example, when you subscribe to e-mail newsletters, participate in competitions or

games, purchase merchandise, etc., you may be required to provide your email address, date of birth and zip code. Further, for example, to the extent we offer such
services, if you order any of our various products, in addition to your name and contact information, we will also collect and may maintain your billing address, shipping
address, product selections, your credit card or other payment instrument information, your order number and information about your computer's internet address and
website which may have referred or directed you to the Services (e.g. the referring URL). Your credit card or debit card number is collected via a secure transmission.
There may be a separate registration process to enter promotions such as contests and sweepstakes which may require the submission of all or some of the following:
your first and last name, street address, city, state and zip code, email address, telephone number and date of birth. Additional information may be requested depending
on the specific promotion, but submission of such information may be optional. The promotion's entry page and/or rules will provide the specific requirements. You may
also have the opportunity to opt-in to receive special promotions or offers from our third party advertisers, sponsors or promotional partners as a result of your use of the
Services in connection with many of these types of promotions.
If we collect such information, in most instances, the applicable page(s) or location(s) within the Services will include statements regarding what information is required for
the elements of the Services to function properly and functionality for you to submit the requested or required information. In addition to the list above, there may also be
opportunities for you to grant permission for use of other of your information in a manner set forth on the applicable page(s) within the Services. You may choose not to
provide certain information, but some of our features require personally identifiable information in order to be accessible and/or operate effectively.
2. How We Collect Your Information
Information You Give Us. We receive and store any information you enter on our Services, submit through emails or other communication, or provide to us in any other
way (including but not limited to: reviews, comments, video submissions, etc.). By submitting such content, you represent and warrant that:
   You are the sole author and owner of the intellectual property rights thereto;
   All “moral rights” that you may have in such content have been voluntarily waived by you;
   All content that you post is accurate;
   You permit to Tennis Channel using the content you supply in accordance with Tennis Channel’s terms of use, and that such submission does not violate those terms.
We may collect information when you interact with the Services, for example, when you subscribe to newsletters, participate in competitions or games or other activities on
our Services, purchase merchandise, etc. When using the Services, you may be asked to provide various types of personally identifiable information or other information
to enhance your experience on the Services.
Automatic Information Collection. We collect information through technology, such as “cookies,” Flash cookies and “Web beacons,” including when you visit our Site
and Application or use our Applications on third-party sites or platforms. Cookies (which may be html files, Flash files or other technology) are small amounts of data which
include a unique string of characters sent to your browser or application from a website's computers and stored on your computer's or device's hard drive that help store
user preferences and activity. Web beacons (also known as pixel tags, image tags, gif or web bugs) are small pieces of code used to collect advertising data, such as
counting page views, promotion views or advertising responses. The Services and/or third parties may use cookies, web beacons and other similar tracking technologies
(collectively, “Tracking Technologies”) to collect information automatically as you browse the Services and the web.
We use Tracking Technologies to help tailor our content, allow users to move between associated sites without logging into each site, understand the Services and
internet usage, improve or customize the content, offerings or advertisements on this Services, personalize your experience on the Services(for example, to recognize you
by name when you return to the Services), understand your interactions with email messages (such as the links clicked on and whether the messages were opened or
forwarded), save your password in password-protected areas, enable you to use shopping carts on the Site, help us offer you products, programs or services that may be
of interest to you, deliver relevant advertising, maintain and administer the Services and for other purposes described in this Privacy Policy.
These Tracking Technologies collect “click stream” data and additional information regarding your visits to the Services (such as your visits to the Site's webpages, use of
our features and purchasing history or preferences), may collect such information across multiple sessions on the Services and other websites offered by our affiliates and
may also collect your IP address or some other identifier unique to the Device you use to access the Services (“Identifier”). An Identifier is automatically assigned to any
Device you use to access the Services. Your personally identifiable information is not collected as part of this process but we may associate anonymous information
collected by Tracking Technologies with personally identifiable information. By visiting the Services, whether as a registered user or otherwise, you acknowledge,

understand and hereby agree that you are giving us your consent to track your activities and your use of the Services through these Tracking Technologies and that we
may use Tracking Technologies in the emails we send to you.
We may additionally use a variety of third party advertising networks, data exchanges, traffic measurement service providers, marketing analytics service providers and
other third parties (collectively, “Third Party Advertising Service Providers”) to, for example, serve advertisements on the Services, facilitate targeting of advertisements
and/or measure and analyze advertising effectiveness and/or traffic on the Services (“Targeting Services”). These Third Party Advertising Service Providers may enable
us to display advertisements based on your visits to the Services and other websites you have visited. Targeting Services enable us to, among other things, help deliver
advertisements or other content to you for products and services that you might be interested in, to prevent you from seeing the same advertisements too many times and
to conduct research regarding the usefulness of certain advertisements to you.
These Third Party Advertising Service Providers do not have access to Tracking Technologies set by the Services except to the extent necessary to provide services to
the Services. The Third Party Advertising Service Providers, as well as advertisers, may themselves set and access their own Tracking Technologies on your Device if
you choose to have Tracking Technologies enabled in your browser (or, for Flash cookies, if you have not removed them) and/or they may otherwise have access to
information about you.
Location Data We Collect. When you use our Service we may solicit your permission to collect your location data. Please be advised, for some features within our
Application to function we must confirm your current location and therefore some features will not be available if you choose not to provide your location data to us. The
specificity of the location data collected may depend on a number of factors, including the Device you are using (e.g. laptop, smartphone, tablet) and how you are
connected to the internet (e.g. via cable broadband connection, WiFi, etc.). If you enable location services for our Application, we may collect location data (e.g. zip code)
periodically as you use or leave open our Application. We may also use this data internally or in conjunction with our third party service providers to customize your
experience and provide offers that may be relevant to you. Depending on the platform you use to access our Application you may be able to control from within the
settings on your Device or the Application(s) whether location data is collected.
Social Networking. When using our Services or when using certain third party social networking services (e.g., Facebook or Twitter) (each and collectively, a “Social
Network”), you may have the option to connect your Services information and activity with your Social Network information and activity and engage with our content on or
through the Social Network, plug-ins and application(s). If you authorize such a connection and engage with our content on or through a Social Network, you permit us to
share or publish information about your activity on our Services, with that Social Network and its users, and to access certain of your Social Network information (e.g.,
name, e-mail address, photo, gender, birthday, location, your list of friends, people you follow and/or who follow you, your posts or 'likes'), as disclosed by you at the time
you consent to the connection, to deliver the content or as part of the operation of the application. We may also obtain non-personally identifiable information (e.g., content
viewed, game performance, high scores, and information about advertisements within the content you have been shown or may have clicked on) from your interaction with
our content. We may combine information which we obtain through social networking sites or applications with information we obtain directly through the Services or from
other sources.
When you allow us to access information from your Social Network account, it can enable us to do things like (1) deliver exclusive content to you, (2) personalize your
online experience with us within and outside our Application(s) or Site(s), and (3) contact you through the social networking sites or directly using your contact information.
By engaging with our content through social networking sites or applications, you consent to the use of this information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. Please note
that when you provide personal information in publicly visible areas of social networking sites or applications, it may be viewed by other members of these sites and we
cannot prevent further use of the information by third parties.
Please keep in mind that when you provide information to us on a third-party site or platform (for example, via our Application), the information you provide may be
separately collected by the third-party site or platform. The information we collect is covered by this Privacy Policy and the information the third-party site or platform
collects is subject to the third-party site or platform’s privacy practices. Privacy choices you have made on the third-party site or platform will not apply to our use of the
information we have collected directly through our Services. To opt out of information collection by a third-party sites or platform, or to obtain information about the
technologies they use or their own privacy policies and practices, please refer to such third-party sites’ or platforms’ privacy policies.
We acquire information from other trusted sources to update or supplement the information you provided or we collected automatically. Local law may require that you
authorize the third party to share your information with us before we can acquire it.
3. How We Use and Share Your Information
If you submit personal information to us, or to any third party acting on our behalf, we may use and share your information as set forth in this Privacy Policy and as
disclosed when you first submit your information. We will not sell, lease, publish or share your personal information with or to anyone else, except as set forth in this

Privacy Policy. We may use and share your personal information as described in Section 1 above for purposes, such as responding to your requests, customizing future
promotions, fulfilling transactions, improving our functionality, and communicating with you, and we may:
     ·        Provide you with access to certain features or functions that we may offer on the Services, such as the option to subscribe to a selection of free email
          newsletters, messaging services, “Find A” feature, or shopping.
     ·    Use your information to provide services you have requested or provide you with offers, promotions, or content or add you to our mailing list.
     ·      Share your information with certain third parties, including service providers, sponsors and promotional partners, so they may help us provide services, offers,
          promotions or content you’ve requested or otherwise in accordance with the application rules of a promotion or terms presented at the time you submit personal
          information, so the third party can administer the promotion, send you offers or content or add you to their mailing list.
     ·     Share your information upon notice posted on an applicable location of our Services where we collect your personal information for an economic transaction and
          notify you that we will be sharing such information with a third party.
     ·        Use and share your information with our third-party survey partners to send you periodic surveys to help improve our Services or your Tennis Channel
          experience.
     ·     Use and share your information in connection with online loyalty, membership or rewards programs operated from our Services or with a third party from which
          you may receive goods or services in connection with such a program.
     ·    Use and share your information with permission from you.
On an aggregate basis only, we collect comprehensive demographic information, and other non-personally identifying information about users of the Services. Such
information can also include your voluntary survey responses, information on how you access and search the Site, and information regarding the domain names and/or IP
addresses of browsers that visit the Site. Tennis Channel will never disclose any personally identifiable information as part of this aggregate information derived from this
personally identifiable information, but we may lend, sell, share or otherwise disclose aggregate information with others so we can perform research and provide the
results to third parties, enhance and market the Services, and conduct accounting and process record keeping functions. We may also collect anonymous information
about you (e.g., your IP address) to personalize your experience and deliver more relevant content and/or advertising messages.
As set forth in this Privacy Policy, we may also share Information with our affiliates.
In general, we collect, store and use your information to provide you with a safe, smooth, efficient and customized experience on the Sites. However, sometimes we need
to collect and use your personal information to enable us to provide technical support, prevent fraud or potentially illegal activities (including copyright infringement), to
enforce our terms of use or rules, to comply with legal process, or in connection with the sale of all of part of our business or transfer of our assets or other merger or
business transfer, or in connection with other corporate transactions.
4. Your Controls and Choices in Managing Your Information
You may choose and control what information you provide about yourself and certain information which is automatically collected via our Services. If you do not wish to
provide certain information necessary for enhanced functionality or content on our Services, please do not use such functionality or content. Your controls and choices
regarding our collection and sharing of your information may include:
     ·    You may correct, update and delete your registration account.
     ·    You may change your choices for subscriptions, newsletters and alerts.
     ·      You may choose whether to receive from us offers and promotions for our products and services, or products and services that we think may be of interest to
          you.
     ·      You may choose whether we share your personal information with other companies so they can send you offers and promotions about their products and
          services.
     ·    You may choose whether to receive targeted advertising from many ad networks, data exchanges, marketing analytics and other service providers.

      ·     You may request access to the personal information we hold about you and that we amend or delete it and we request third parties with whom we have shared
           the information do the same.
If you do not want information collected through the use of cookies, there is a simple procedure in most browsers that allows a user to accept or reject most cookies.
Certain cookies that are set when some video products are accessed on our Site, called local shared objects or Flash cookies, may not be managed using the settings in
your web browser. Information on managing, accepting and rejecting these cookies is available from Adobe on the Adobe website. If you set your browser or Adobe
Flash options not to accept cookies or local shared objects, you may not be able to take advantage of certain Services.
Tennis Channel has implemented procedures for you to access, correct or delete your personally identifiable information. To access your personally identifiable
information, send an e-mail with the word “Privacy” in the subject line to Privacy@tennischannel.com, or write to the Tennis Channel Internet Privacy Information at The
Tennis Channel, Inc., Business and Legal Affairs, 2850 Ocean Park Blvd., Suite 150, Santa Monica, California 90405, requesting a listing of the personally identifiable
information that is on file that you have provided or that has been obtained from a third party. Tennis Channel will provide you with a list of your personally identifiable
information within thirty (30) calendar days from receipt of your request. There may be certain instances when Tennis Channel may not be able to provide the personally
identifiable information, such as when access would violate the privacy of another individual or when access is prohibited by law.
In the event the personally identifiable information on file is incorrect, you may correct the personally identifiable information by sending a written request for correction to
Tennis Channel Internet Privacy Information at The Tennis Channel, Inc., Business and Legal Affairs, 2850 Ocean Park Blvd., Suite 150, Santa Monica, California 90405,
including (1) all of the incorrect personally identifiable information, (2) the corrections that you wish to make to your personally identifiable information, and (3) your
signature authorizing such changes. Tennis Channel will then correct the personally identifiable information in its database and send a written confirmation to you within
forty-five (45) business days.
If for any reason you wish to stop all future communications from the Tennis Channel site(s), you may send an e-mail with the word "Privacy" in the subject line to
Privacy@tennischannel.com, or write to Tennis Channel Internet Privacy Information at The Tennis Channel, Inc., Business and Legal Affairs, 2850 Ocean Park Blvd.,
Suite 150, Santa Monica, California 90405, requesting that your personally identifiable information be permanently removed from the Tennis Channel's website database.
Tennis Channel will send a written confirmation of such removal to you within thirty (30) calendar days of receipt of your request. E-mails sent to
Privacy@tennischannel.com for purposes other than communication about personally identifiable information may not be acknowledged or responded to.
5. Children’s Privacy
Tennis Channel operates general audience Websites, and does not knowingly collect, retain, or use personally identifiable information from children under thirteen (13)
years of age. Accordingly, children under the age of thirteen (13) may be restricted from participating in certain features and transactions on the Services.
6. Security
Tennis Channel uses reasonable administrative, technical, personnel and physical measures to safeguard personally identifiable information in its possession against
loss, theft and unauthorized use, disclosure or modification. In addition, Tennis Channel uses reasonable methods to make sure that personally identifiable information is
accurate, up-to-date and appropriately complete.
7. Changes to This Privacy Policy
From time to time Tennis Channel may revise this Privacy Policy to reflect industry initiatives or changes in the law, our personally identifiable information collection and
use practices, the features of our Site(s) or technology. If we make revisions that change the way we collect or use your personally identifiable information, those changes
will be posted in this Privacy Policy and the effective date will be noted at the beginning of this Privacy Policy.
8. Comments and Questions
If you have a comment or question about this Privacy Policy, please contact us:
           The Tennis Channel, Inc.

         Business & Legal Affairs
         2850 Ocean Park Blvd., Suite 150
         Santa Monica, California 90405
         Telephone: (310) 314-9400
         Email: Privacy@tennischannel.com
9. California Privacy Rights
If you are a California resident, California Civil Code Section 1798.82 permits you to request certain information regarding our disclosure of your personally identifiable
information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please contact us at:
         The Tennis Channel, Inc.
         Business & Legal Affairs
         2850 Ocean Park Blvd., Suite 150
         Santa Monica, California 90405
         Telephone: (310) 314-9400
         Email: Privacy@tennischannel.com
© 2014 The Tennis Channel, Inc. All rights reserved.
Use of this Site signifies your acceptance of this Privacy Policy and the Terms of Use for TennisChannel.com.
